<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss xmlns:ns0="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>lovelyRSS - Latest Posts</title>
    <description>Latest posts from all subscribed feeds</description>
    <link>https://github.com</link>
    <lastBuildDate>2025-07-30 18:08:39 UTC</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>lovelyRSS/1.0</generator>
    <ns0:link href="./latest_rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Fast</title>
      <link>https://www.catherinejue.com/fast</link>
      <description>Article URL: https://www.catherinejue.com/fast Comments URL: https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=44736967 Points: 6 # Comments: 1</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 17:21:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.catherinejue.com/fast</guid>
      <source url="https://hnrss.org/frontpage">Hacker News</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Artie (YC S23) Is Hiring Founding AEs</title>
      <link>https://www.ycombinator.com/companies/artie/jobs/CfSrcAH-founding-ae</link>
      <description>Article URL: https://www.ycombinator.com/companies/artie/jobs/CfSrcAH-founding-ae Comments URL: https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=44736673 Points: 0 # Comments: 0</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 17:01:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.ycombinator.com/companies/artie/jobs/CfSrcAH-founding-ae</guid>
      <source url="https://hnrss.org/frontpage">Hacker News</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What's Not to Like?</title>
      <link>https://theamericanscholar.org/whats-not-to-like/</link>
      <description>Article URL: https://theamericanscholar.org/whats-not-to-like/ Comments URL: https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=44736668 Points: 7 # Comments: 3</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 17:00:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://theamericanscholar.org/whats-not-to-like/</guid>
      <source url="https://hnrss.org/frontpage">Hacker News</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australia widens teen social media ban to YouTube, scraps exemption</title>
      <link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/australia-widens-teen-social-media-ban-youtube-scraps-exemption-2025-07-29/</link>
      <description>Article URL: https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/australia-widens-teen-social-media-ban-youtube-scraps-exemption-2025-07-29/ Comments URL: https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=44736646 Points: 29 # Comments: 16</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 16:59:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/australia-widens-teen-social-media-ban-youtube-scraps-exemption-2025-07-29/</guid>
      <source url="https://hnrss.org/frontpage">Hacker News</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crush: Glamourous AI coding agent for your favourite terminal</title>
      <link>https://github.com/charmbracelet/crush</link>
      <description>Article URL: https://github.com/charmbracelet/crush Comments URL: https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=44736176 Points: 150 # Comments: 79</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 16:18:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://github.com/charmbracelet/crush</guid>
      <source url="https://hnrss.org/frontpage">Hacker News</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critical Vulnerability in AI Vibe Coding platform Base44</title>
      <link>https://www.wiz.io/blog/critical-vulnerability-base44</link>
      <description>Article URL: https://www.wiz.io/blog/critical-vulnerability-base44 Comments URL: https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=44736101 Points: 23 # Comments: 11</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 16:12:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.wiz.io/blog/critical-vulnerability-base44</guid>
      <source url="https://hnrss.org/frontpage">Hacker News</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optician Sans – A free font based on historical eye charts and optotypes</title>
      <link>https://optician-sans.com/</link>
      <description>Article URL: https://optician-sans.com/ Comments URL: https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=44736090 Points: 54 # Comments: 6</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 16:11:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://optician-sans.com/</guid>
      <source url="https://hnrss.org/frontpage">Hacker News</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A practical guide on how to use the GitHub MCP server</title>
      <link>https://github.blog/ai-and-ml/generative-ai/a-practical-guide-on-how-to-use-the-github-mcp-server/</link>
      <description>Upgrade from a local MCP Docker image to GitHub’s hosted server and automate pull requests, continuous integration, and security triage in minutes — no tokens required. The post A practical guide on how to use the GitHub MCP server appeared first on The GitHub Blog.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://github.blog/ai-and-ml/generative-ai/a-practical-guide-on-how-to-use-the-github-mcp-server/</guid>
      <source url="https://github.blog/feed/">GitHub Blog</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Launch HN: Lucidic (YC W25) – Debug, test, and evaluate AI agents in production</title>
      <link>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=44735843</link>
      <description>Hi HN, we’re Abhinav, Andy, and Jeremy, and we’re building Lucidic AI (https://dashboard.lucidic.ai), an AI agent interpretability tool to help observe/debug AI agents.Here is a demo: https://youtu.be/Zvoh1QUMhXQ.Getting started is easy with just one line of code. You just call lai.init() in your agent code and log into the dashboard. You can see traces of each run, cumulative trends across sessions, built-in or custom evals, and grouped failure modes. Call lai.create_step() with any metadata you want, memory snapshots, tool outputs, stateful info, and we'll index it for debugging.We did NLP research at Stanford AI Lab (SAIL), where we worked on creating an AI agent (w/ fine-tuned models and DSPy) to solve math olympiad problems (focusing on AIME/USAMO); and we realized debugging these agents was hard. But the last straw was when we built an e-commerce agent that could buy items online. It kept failing at checkout, and every one-line change, tweaking a prompt, switching to Llama, adjusting tool logic, meant another 10-minute rerun just to see if we hit the same checkout page.At this point, we were all like, this sucks, so we improved agent interpretability with better debugging, monitoring, and evals.We started by listening to users who told us traditional LLM observability platforms don't capture the complexity of agents. Agents have tools, memories, events, not just input/output pairs. So we automatically transform OTel (and/or regular) agent logs into interactive graph visualizations that cluster similar states based on memory and action patterns. We heard that people wanted to test small changes even with the graphs, so we created “time traveling,” where you can modify any state (memory contents, tool outputs, context), then re-simulate 30–40 times to see outcome distributions. We embed the responses, cluster by similarity, and show which modifications lead to stable vs. divergent behaviors.Then we saw people running their agent 10 times on the same task, watching each run individually, and wasting hours looking at mostly repeated states. So we built trajectory clustering on similar state embeddings (like similar tools or memories) to surface behavioral patterns across mass simulations.We then use that to create a force-directed layout that automatically groups similar paths your agent took, which displays states as nodes, actions as edges, and failure probability as color intensity. The clusters make failure patterns obvious; you see trends across hundreds of runs, not individual traces.Finally, when people saw our observability features, they naturally wanted evaluation capabilities. So we developed a concept for people to make their own evals called "rubrics," which lets you define specific criteria, assign weights to each criterion, and set score definitions, giving you a structured way to measure agent performance against your exact requirements.To evaluate these criteria, we used our own platform to build an investigator agent that reviews your criteria and evaluates performance much more effectively than traditional LLM-as-a-judge approaches.To get started visit dashboard.lucidic.ai and https://docs.lucidic.ai/getting-started/quickstart. You can use it for free for 1,000 event and step creations.Look forward to your thoughts! And don’t hesitate to reach out at team@lucidic.ai Comments URL: https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=44735843 Points: 52 # Comments: 14</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 15:54:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=44735843</guid>
      <source url="https://hnrss.org/frontpage">Hacker News</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Words about Arrays and Tables</title>
      <link>https://buttondown.com/hillelwayne/archive/2000-words-about-arrays-and-tables/</link>
      <description>Article URL: https://buttondown.com/hillelwayne/archive/2000-words-about-arrays-and-tables/ Comments URL: https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=44735334 Points: 38 # Comments: 10</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 15:15:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://buttondown.com/hillelwayne/archive/2000-words-about-arrays-and-tables/</guid>
      <source url="https://hnrss.org/frontpage">Hacker News</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Show HN: A High-Altitude Low-Power Flight Computer for High-Altitude Balloons</title>
      <link>https://github.com/New-England-Weather-Balloon-Society/Tiny4FSK</link>
      <description>I've been working on this for a while now, and I'm happy to share!I've been into launching weather balloons for a few years. One aspect of the hobby that really drew me in was the tracking side of things. Tracking systems let you follow the balloon's position throughout the flight and, most importantly, know exactly where it lands so you can recover the instrumentation. APRS is what I started out using during my first few years in the hobby, after I got my amateur radio license in 2020 (W0MXX). I designed a few small boards using the trackuino (https://github.com/trackuino/trackuino) firmware (while breaking 3 $70 radio modules along the way).I then got into recovering radiosondes, which are launched twice per day by the NWS and can be reprogrammed using RS41ng (https://github.com/mikaelnousiainen/RS41ng) to run many amateur radio tracking protocols. I was a bit dissatisfied with how large and heavy the radiosonde trackers were, so I designed my own tracking system, called Tiny4FSK.Tiny4FSK is a flight computer with built-in tracking using the Horus Binary v2 tracking system. This protocol was developed by the Project Horus team specifically for high-altitude balloons, and it brings features like high transmit rates, forward error correction, and excellent weak-signal performance in an open source package. It's designed to be as compact as possible and can run on a single AA battery for upwards of 17 hours.The main board comes with header rows that allow for out-of-the-box expansion. I developed a shield that supports the BME280 environmental sensor, the ICM-20948 9-axis IMU, and more via the Qwiic connector. It also features an OLED display for basic diagnostics.While I've pretty much polished the main tracking procedures (and have tested on multiple flights), I'm still developing the IMU code using a lightweight Kalman filter. Additionally, there isn't yet a wide network of Horus Binary decoding stations like the APRS network has (I-gates), but I hope that by promoting this protocol, more stations will pop up. This means that if you're not in an area with many receive stations, you'll need to set up your own using either Horus-GUI (https://github.com/projecthorus/horus-gui) or horusdemodlib (https://github.com/projecthorus/horusdemodlib).One issue I’m still working on is improving RF signal strength. Although the protocol is decodable in very low-noise environments, the transmit power appears to be lower than that of a typical radiosonde. This could be due to several factors: limited current on a weak power source (signal is stronger when powered from a bench supply), off-tuned filtering/matching, or not paying enough attention to the antenna. I'm planning to run more simulations to figure this out. That said, the signal is still decodable from the ground even at max altitude (~100,000 feet).On the more technical side, Tiny4FSK uses: - the SAMD21 microcontroller, which is an ARM Cortex-M0+ MCU - the TPS61200 boost converter, which is adjusted to output 3.3v - Si4063 radio module, which I use on the 70cm band - ATGM336H gps module - pretty cheap GPS module which works in airborne mode (&gt;18km) - integrated BME280 temperature, pressure, and humidity sensor The code uses the Arduino framework to make it accessible to beginners.All flights using Horus Binary v2, including reprogrammed radiosondes, other custom trackers, and Tiny4FSK show up in real-time on Sondehub Amateur (https://amateur.sondehub.org). Flight data can be found in the /Media/Data folder on Github (there's several missing flights on there though).Thanks for reading, hope I didn’t mess anything up too badly in the post! -Max Comments URL: https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=44734983 Points: 13 # Comments: 10</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 14:51:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://github.com/New-England-Weather-Balloon-Society/Tiny4FSK</guid>
      <source url="https://hnrss.org/frontpage">Hacker News</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NMDA Receptor Antagonists: Slightly More Than You Wanted to Know</title>
      <link>https://grillbert.substack.com/p/nmda-receptor-antagonists-a-bit-more</link>
      <description>Article URL: https://grillbert.substack.com/p/nmda-receptor-antagonists-a-bit-more Comments URL: https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=44734260 Points: 22 # Comments: 8</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 13:55:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://grillbert.substack.com/p/nmda-receptor-antagonists-a-bit-more</guid>
      <source url="https://hnrss.org/frontpage">Hacker News</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitmapist: We built an open-source cohorts analytics tool that saved millions</title>
      <link>https://www.doist.dev/bitmapist/</link>
      <description>Article URL: https://www.doist.dev/bitmapist/ Comments URL: https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=44733983 Points: 42 # Comments: 3</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 13:33:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.doist.dev/bitmapist/</guid>
      <source url="https://hnrss.org/frontpage">Hacker News</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Writing memory efficient C structs</title>
      <link>https://tomscheers.github.io/2025/07/29/writing-memory-efficient-structs-post.html</link>
      <description>Article URL: https://tomscheers.github.io/2025/07/29/writing-memory-efficient-structs-post.html Comments URL: https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=44733968 Points: 66 # Comments: 20</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 13:32:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://tomscheers.github.io/2025/07/29/writing-memory-efficient-structs-post.html</guid>
      <source url="https://hnrss.org/frontpage">Hacker News</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Show HN: An AI agent that learns your product and guides your users</title>
      <link>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=44733892</link>
      <description>Hey HN! My name is Christian, and I’m the co-founder of https://frigade.ai. We’ve built a powerful AI agent that automatically learns how to use any web-based product, and in turn guides users directly in the UI, automatically generates documentation, and even takes actions on a user’s behalf. Think of it as Clippy from the old MS Office. But on steroids. And actually helpful.You can see the agent and tool-calling SDK in action here: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UPe0t3A1VpgHow is this different from other AI customer support products?Most AI "copilots" are really just glorified chatbots. They skim your help center and spit out some nonspecific bullet points. Basically some ‘hopes and prayers’ that your users will figure it out. Ultimately, this puts the burden on the user to follow through. And assumes companies are keeping their help center up-to-date with every product change. That means constant screenshots of new product UI or features for accurate instructions.These solutions leverage only a fraction of what’s possible with AI, which can now reason about software interfaces extensively.With Frigade AI, we guide the user directly in the product and build on-demand tours based on the current user’s state and context. The agents can also take actions immediately on a user’s behalf, e.g. inviting a colleague to a workspace or retrieving billing information (via our tool calling SDK).This was only made possible recently. The latest frontier models (GPT 4.1, Claude 4, Gemini 2.5, etc.) are able to reason about UIs and workflows in a way that simply didn’t work just 6 months ago. That’s why we’re so excited to bring this technology to the forefront of complex legacy SaaS applications that are not yet AI enabled.How does it work?1. Invite agent@frigade.ai to your product. You can send multiple invitations based on distinct roles.2. Our agent automatically explores and reasons about your application.3. Attach any existing help center resources or training documentation to supplement the agent’s understanding. Totally optional.4. Install the agent assistant Javascript snippet (just a few lines).5. That’s it. Your users can now start asking questions and get on demand product tours and questions answered in real time without any overhead.This process takes only a few minutes. Once running, you can improve the agent by rating and providing feedback to the responses it provides. If you want to integrate further, you can also hook up your own code to our tool calling SDK to enable the agent to look up customer info, issue refunds, etc. directly. These calls can be made with just a few lines of code by describing the tool and its parameters in natural language and passing a single Javascript promise (e.g. make an API call, call a function in your app, etc.).Would love to hear what the HN crowd thinks about this approach! Are you building your own AI agent from scratch, or looking to embed one off the shelf? Comments URL: https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=44733892 Points: 11 # Comments: 7</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 13:24:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=44733892</guid>
      <source url="https://hnrss.org/frontpage">Hacker News</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Try the Mosquito Bucket of Death</title>
      <link>https://www.energyvanguard.com/blog/try-the-mosquito-bucket-of-death/</link>
      <description>Article URL: https://www.energyvanguard.com/blog/try-the-mosquito-bucket-of-death/ Comments URL: https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=44733888 Points: 222 # Comments: 194</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 13:24:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.energyvanguard.com/blog/try-the-mosquito-bucket-of-death/</guid>
      <source url="https://hnrss.org/frontpage">Hacker News</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Our $100M Series B</title>
      <link>https://oxide.computer/blog/our-100m-series-b</link>
      <description>Article URL: https://oxide.computer/blog/our-100m-series-b Comments URL: https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=44733817 Points: 479 # Comments: 303</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 13:17:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://oxide.computer/blog/our-100m-series-b</guid>
      <source url="https://hnrss.org/frontpage">Hacker News</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Show HN: MoebiusXBIN – ASCII and text-mode art editor with custom font support</title>
      <link>https://blog.glyphdrawing.club/moebiusxbin-ascii-and-text-mode-art-editor-with-custom-font-support/</link>
      <description>Article URL: https://blog.glyphdrawing.club/moebiusxbin-ascii-and-text-mode-art-editor-with-custom-font-support/ Comments URL: https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=44733742 Points: 37 # Comments: 2</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 13:11:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://blog.glyphdrawing.club/moebiusxbin-ascii-and-text-mode-art-editor-with-custom-font-support/</guid>
      <source url="https://hnrss.org/frontpage">Hacker News</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Making Libcurl Work in WebAssembly</title>
      <link>https://jeroen.github.io/notes/webassembly-curl/</link>
      <description>Article URL: https://jeroen.github.io/notes/webassembly-curl/ Comments URL: https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=44733734 Points: 33 # Comments: 5</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 13:09:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://jeroen.github.io/notes/webassembly-curl/</guid>
      <source url="https://hnrss.org/frontpage">Hacker News</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why do we all remember the same things differently?</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/shorts/1KnTEjxFM0E</link>
      <description>We made this video in partnership with Unlikely Collaborators. Our memories aren’t perfect records of the past — they’re reconstructions shaped by brain activity. Neuroscientists Lisa Genova and André Fenton explain that a memory is created through neural patterns that can subtly shift each time we recall it. We may unknowingly add or lose details over time. Understanding this science helps us approach memory with more humility and empathy, and deepens our insight into how memories shape one’s identity and beliefs. About André Fenton: André Fenton, PhD, is a neuroscientist and professor at NYU’s Center for Neural Science. He co-discovered PKMzeta, a key molecule for long-term memory, and studies how the brain stores and retrieves information. His work explores cognition, mental illness, and memory disorders. Fenton also founded Bio‑Signal Group, which created an FDA-approved portable EEG. About Lisa Genova: Lisa Genova, PhD, is a neuroscientist and bestselling author with a Ph.D. from Harvard. Her debut novel, Still Alice, explored early-onset Alzheimer’s and became an Oscar-winning film. Through novels like Left Neglected and Inside the O’Briens, she blends neuroscience and storytelling to humanize brain disorders.</description>
      <pubDate>2025-07-30T13:00:02+00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.youtube.com/shorts/1KnTEjxFM0E</guid>
      <source url="https://www.youtube.com/feeds/videos.xml?channel_id=UCvQECJukTDE2i6aCoMnS-Vg">Big Think</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Problem Solving Is Often a Matter of Cooking Up an Appropriate Markov Chain</title>
      <link>https://www.jstor.org/stable/41548580</link>
      <description>Article URL: https://www.jstor.org/stable/41548580 Comments URL: https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=44733341 Points: 133 # Comments: 34</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 12:29:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.jstor.org/stable/41548580</guid>
      <source url="https://hnrss.org/frontpage">Hacker News</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The HTML Hobbyist</title>
      <link>https://www.htmlhobbyist.com/</link>
      <description>Article URL: https://www.htmlhobbyist.com/ Comments URL: https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=44733119 Points: 155 # Comments: 78</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 12:03:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.htmlhobbyist.com/</guid>
      <source url="https://hnrss.org/frontpage">Hacker News</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dating safety app Tea suspends messaging after hack</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/cd0dgkjgzvjo?at_medium=RSS&amp;at_campaign=rss</link>
      <description>It comes after a hack which exposed thousands of members' images, posts and comments.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 10:01:32 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/cd0dgkjgzvjo?at_medium=RSS&amp;at_campaign=rss</guid>
      <source url="http://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/technology/rss.xml">BBC Technology</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YouTube to be included in Australia's teen social media ban</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/cpv0zkxx0njo?at_medium=RSS&amp;at_campaign=rss</link>
      <description>The Australian government says the world-first ban is aimed at protecting youth from online harm.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 01:24:49 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/cpv0zkxx0njo?at_medium=RSS&amp;at_campaign=rss</guid>
      <source url="http://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/technology/rss.xml">BBC Technology</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tech Life</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.co.uk/sounds/play/w3ct6zp1?at_medium=RSS&amp;at_campaign=rss</link>
      <description>What will the era of Agentic AI offer us ?</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 19:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bbc.co.uk/sounds/play/w3ct6zp1?at_medium=RSS&amp;at_campaign=rss</guid>
      <source url="http://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/technology/rss.xml">BBC Technology</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Developers remain willing but reluctant to use AI: The 2025 Developer Survey results are here</title>
      <link>https://stackoverflow.blog/2025/07/29/developers-remain-willing-but-reluctant-to-use-ai-the-2025-developer-survey-results-are-here/</link>
      <description>No need to bury the lede: more developers are using AI tools, but their trust in those tools is falling.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://stackoverflow.blog/2025/07/29/developers-remain-willing-but-reluctant-to-use-ai-the-2025-developer-survey-results-are-here/</guid>
      <source url="https://stackoverflow.blog/feed/">Stack Overflow Blog</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From first commits to big ships: Tune into our new open source podcast</title>
      <link>https://github.blog/open-source/maintainers/from-first-commits-to-big-ships-tune-into-our-new-open-source-podcast/</link>
      <description>Introducing the brand new GitHub Podcast: A show dedicated to the topics, trends, stories, and culture in and around the open source developer community on GitHub. The post From first commits to big ships: Tune into our new open source podcast appeared first on The GitHub Blog.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 16:31:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://github.blog/open-source/maintainers/from-first-commits-to-big-ships-tune-into-our-new-open-source-podcast/</guid>
      <source url="https://github.blog/feed/">GitHub Blog</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Let's Kill You a Billion Times to Make You Immortal</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7wK4peez9zE</link>
      <description>Go to https://ground.news/KiN to get 40% off unlimited access to Ground News so you can compare coverage and think critically about the news you read. Students get 10% off in our Back to School collection! https://shop.kgs.link/back2school Explore inspiring posters and stationery from the kurzgesagt shop – designed to turn your workspace into a curiosity-powered study zone. Sources &amp; further reading: https://sites.google.com/view/sources-quantum-immortality/ No matter how likely your death is, there will always be a version of you that survives. At least according to one of the most bizarre interpretations of quantum mechanics, known as Quantum Immortality. Can science prove that you are unkillable? And does this mean our reality is split into an endless number of copies? OUR CHANNELS ▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀ German: https://kgs.link/youtubeDE Spanish: https://kgs.link/youtubeES French: https://kgs.link/youtubeFR Portuguese: https://kgs.link/youtubePT Arabic: https://kgs.link/youtubeAR Hindi: https://kgs.link/youtubeHI Japanese: https://kgs.link/youtubeJA Korean: https://kgs.link/youtubeKO HOW CAN YOU SUPPORT US? ▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀ This is how we make our living and it would be a pleasure if you support us! Get Products designed with ❤️ https://shop.kgs.link Join the Patreon Bird Army 🐧 https://kgs.link/patreon DISCUSSIONS &amp; SOCIAL MEDIA ▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀ Instagram: https://kgs.link/instagram TikTok: https://kgs.link/tiktok Reddit: https://kgs.link/reddit Discord: https://kgs.link/discord Twitter: https://kgs.link/twitter Bluesky: https://kgs.link/bluesky Facebook: https://kgs.link/facebook Newsletter: https://kgs.link/newsletter OUR VOICE ▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀ The kurzgesagt voice is from Steve Taylor: https://kgs.link/youtube-voice OUR MUSIC ♬♪ ▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀ 700+ minutes of kurzgesagt soundtracks by Epic Mountain: Spotify: https://kgs.link/music-spotify Soundcloud: https://kgs.link/music-soundcloud Bandcamp: https://kgs.link/music-bandcamp Youtube: https://kgs.link/music-youtube Facebook: https://kgs.link/music-facebook The soundtrack of this video: SoundCloud: https://bit.ly/40vijCu Bandcamp: https://bit.ly/46TSXSv If you want to help us caption this video, please send subtitles to subtitle@kurzgesagt.org You can find info on what subtitle files work on YouTube here: https://support.google.com/youtube/answer/2734698?hl=en-GB&amp;ref_topic=7296214 Thank you! 🐦🐧🐤 PATREON BIRD ARMY 🐤🐧🐦 ▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀ Many thanks to our wonderful Patreons (from http://kgs.link/patreon) who support us every month and made this video possible: Pawel, Signe Ozola, Leon Baran, ThreefromTwo, Micaela Jennings, Jake Hopkins, DamienVV, Hougle, Stefan Kraft, ICE, Alessandro Crespi, Amory D, MC Brawl, Titus, Eric Chagnon, Saif AlNajjar, Redcheshire, Gergely Garai</description>
      <pubDate>2025-07-29T14:00:02+00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7wK4peez9zE</guid>
      <source url="https://www.youtube.com/feeds/videos.xml?channel_id=UCsXVk37bltHxD1rDPwtNM8Q">Kurzgesagt – In a Nutshell</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Jesus and Socrates taught the same way</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_A0JV_4kMXA</link>
      <description>This interview is an episode from ‪ @The-Well, our publication about ideas that inspire a life well-lived, created with the ‪@JohnTempletonFoundation. Subscribe to The Well on YouTube ► https://bit.ly/thewell-youtube Watch The Well’s next interview with Betül Kaçar ► The ocean is evolving, and it’s not based on the ‘survival of the fittest’ https://youtu.be/nl_-nmZ4_Xc What if religious texts were some of our most significant sources of philosophical insight? Philosopher Meghan Sullivan believes that traditions like Christianity, Judaism, and Islam are filled with moral questions that invite discussion and reflection. She challenges the idea that philosophy must be strictly secular, pointing out how religious stories and parables often resemble the open-ended questioning found in ancient dialogues like Plato’s Republic. These connections support the idea that religious texts are not meant to shut down debate, but encourage it. For Sullivan, exploring faith through philosophical conversation helps us think more clearly about how to live and what it means to be human. Read the video transcript ►https://bigthink.com/the-well/why-philosophy-needs-religion?utm_source=youtube&amp;utm_medium=video&amp;utm_campaign=youtube_description_bigthink ---------------------------------------------------------------------------------- About Meghan Sullivan: Meghan Sullivan is the Wilsey Family College Professor of Philosophy at the University of Notre Dame, where she leads the Ethics Initiative and founded the Institute for Ethics and the Common Good. With support from the John Templeton Foundation, the Institute advances research and teaching on human flourishing. Sullivan’s work spans ethics, metaphysics, and religion. She’s the author of Time Biases and co-author of The Good Life Method, based on her acclaimed course “God and the Good Life.” ---------------------------------------------------------------------------------- About The Well Do we inhabit a multiverse? Do we have free will? What is love? Is evolution directional? There are no simple answers to life’s biggest questions, and that’s why they’re the questions occupying the world’s brightest minds. Together, let's learn from them. Subscribe to the weekly newsletter ► https://bit.ly/thewellemailsignup ---------------------------------------------------------------------------------- Join The Well on your favorite platforms: ► Facebook: https://bit.ly/thewellFB ► Instagram: https://bit.ly/thewellIG</description>
      <pubDate>2025-07-29T13:01:07+00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_A0JV_4kMXA</guid>
      <source url="https://www.youtube.com/feeds/videos.xml?channel_id=UCvQECJukTDE2i6aCoMnS-Vg">Big Think</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minister must apologise over Savile claim, says Farage</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/cgery3eeqzxo?at_medium=RSS&amp;at_campaign=rss</link>
      <description>Minister Peter Kyle claims that by opposing online safety laws the Reform UK leader is siding with sex offenders.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 11:28:07 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/cgery3eeqzxo?at_medium=RSS&amp;at_campaign=rss</guid>
      <source url="http://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/technology/rss.xml">BBC Technology</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EE to launch phone plans which restrict internet for teens</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/cvg3lgdv3r7o?at_medium=RSS&amp;at_campaign=rss</link>
      <description>UK mobile network operators are already required to ensure only adults can access adult content while using their network.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 11:11:08 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/cvg3lgdv3r7o?at_medium=RSS&amp;at_campaign=rss</guid>
      <source url="http://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/technology/rss.xml">BBC Technology</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google launches new AI search feature in UK</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/clyj4zky4zwo?at_medium=RSS&amp;at_campaign=rss</link>
      <description>The new tool marks a significant change for the search giant but raises questions for advertisers.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 08:43:59 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/clyj4zky4zwo?at_medium=RSS&amp;at_campaign=rss</guid>
      <source url="http://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/technology/rss.xml">BBC Technology</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>That custom gift for your mom takes more work than you think</title>
      <link>https://stackoverflow.blog/2025/07/29/that-custom-gift-for-your-mom-takes-more-work-than-you-think/</link>
      <description>Ryan welcomes Mahir Yavuz, Senior Director of Engineering at Etsy, to the show to explore the unique challenges that Etsy’s marketplace faces and how Etsy’s teams leverage machine learning and AI to manage product SKUs, enrich inventory metadata, and improve both buyer and seller experiences.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 07:40:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://stackoverflow.blog/2025/07/29/that-custom-gift-for-your-mom-takes-more-work-than-you-think/</guid>
      <source url="https://stackoverflow.blog/feed/">Stack Overflow Blog</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Could aluminium become the packaging 'champion'?</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/ce3nw5vnzgpo?at_medium=RSS&amp;at_campaign=rss</link>
      <description>Some packaging firms say aluminium could be used more widely in packaging, but cost may hold it back</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 23:04:41 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/ce3nw5vnzgpo?at_medium=RSS&amp;at_campaign=rss</guid>
      <source url="http://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/technology/rss.xml">BBC Technology</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scaling for impact: How GitHub Copilot supercharges smallholder farmers</title>
      <link>https://github.blog/open-source/social-impact/scaling-for-impact-how-github-copilot-supercharges-smallholder-farmers/</link>
      <description>Empowering 10 million farm families by 2030 to generate $1 billion in new revenue. How GitHub helps One Acre Fund’s mission — driving real impact across Africa. The post Scaling for impact: How GitHub Copilot supercharges smallholder farmers appeared first on The GitHub Blog.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 19:53:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://github.blog/open-source/social-impact/scaling-for-impact-how-github-copilot-supercharges-smallholder-farmers/</guid>
      <source url="https://github.blog/feed/">GitHub Blog</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VPNs top download charts as age verification law kicks in</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/cn72ydj70g5o?at_medium=RSS&amp;at_campaign=rss</link>
      <description>Experts say free versions of such apps or services may carry potential security and privacy risks.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 14:25:21 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/cn72ydj70g5o?at_medium=RSS&amp;at_campaign=rss</guid>
      <source url="http://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/technology/rss.xml">BBC Technology</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The beauty of ideals</title>
      <link>https://world.hey.com/dhh/the-beauty-of-ideals-b3dccf72</link>
      <description>Ideals are supposed to be unattainable for the great many. If everyone could be the smartest, strongest, prettiest, or best, there would be no need for ideals — we'd all just be perfect. But we're not, so ideals exist to show us the peak of humanity and to point our ambition and appreciation toward it.This is what I always hated about the 90s. It was a decade that made it cool to be a loser. It was the decade of MTV's Beavis and Butt-Head. It was the age of grunge. I'm generationally obliged to like Nirvana, but what a perfectly depressive, suicidal soundtrack to loser culture.Naomi Wolf's The Beauty Myth was published in 1990. It took a critical theory-like lens on beauty ideals, and finding it all so awfully oppressive. Because, actually, seeing beautiful, slim people in advertising or media is bad. Because we don't all look like that! And who's even to say what "beauty" is, anyway? It's all just socially constructed! The final stage of that dead-end argument appeared as an ad here in Copenhagen thirty years later during the 2020 insanity: I passed it every day biking the boys to school for weeks. Next to other slim, fit Danes also riding their bikes. None of whom resembled the grotesque display of obesity towering over them on their commute from Calvin Klein.While this campaign was laughably out of place in Copenhagen, it's possible that it brought recognition and representation in some parts of America. But a celebration of ideals it was not.That's the problem with the whole "representation" narrative. It proposes we're all better off if all we see is a mirror of ourselves, however obese, lazy, ignorant, or incompetent, because at least it won't be "unrealistic". Screw that. The last thing we need is a patronizing message that however little you try, you're perfect just the way you are.No, the beauty of ideals is that they ask more of us. Ask us to pursue knowledge, fitness, and competence by taking inspiration from the best human specimens.Thankfully, no amount of post-modern deconstruction or academic theory babble seems capable of suppressing the intrinsic human yearning for excellence forever. The ideals are finally starting to emerge again.</description>
      <pubDate>2025-07-28T10:31:34Z</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://world.hey.com/dhh/the-beauty-of-ideals-b3dccf72</guid>
      <source url="https://world.hey.com/dhh/feed.atom">David Heinemeier Hansson</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google failed to warn 10 million of Turkey earthquake severity</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/c77v2kx304go?at_medium=RSS&amp;at_campaign=rss</link>
      <description>The tech giant said only 469 serious warnings were sent out ahead of the 7.8 magnitude quake.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 23:16:50 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/c77v2kx304go?at_medium=RSS&amp;at_campaign=rss</guid>
      <source url="http://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/technology/rss.xml">BBC Technology</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EE says latest outage fixed after 'technical fault'</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/cx2q8qw0q0go?at_medium=RSS&amp;at_campaign=rss</link>
      <description>The mobile phone service provider says it carried out work overnight after customers reported problems.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 19:02:36 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/cx2q8qw0q0go?at_medium=RSS&amp;at_campaign=rss</guid>
      <source url="http://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/technology/rss.xml">BBC Technology</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers steal images from women's dating safety app that vets men</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/c7vl57n74pqo?at_medium=RSS&amp;at_campaign=rss</link>
      <description>Thousands of women registered with Tea have had their images illegally accessed, the US firm says.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 13:58:47 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/c7vl57n74pqo?at_medium=RSS&amp;at_campaign=rss</guid>
      <source url="http://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/technology/rss.xml">BBC Technology</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tech Now</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.co.uk/iplayer/episode/m002gm6k?at_medium=RSS&amp;at_campaign=rss</link>
      <description>Yasmin Morgan-Griffiths has exclusive access to La Sagrada Familia in Barcelona.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 01:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bbc.co.uk/iplayer/episode/m002gm6k?at_medium=RSS&amp;at_campaign=rss</guid>
      <source url="http://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/technology/rss.xml">BBC Technology</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to build secure and scalable remote MCP servers</title>
      <link>https://github.blog/ai-and-ml/generative-ai/how-to-build-secure-and-scalable-remote-mcp-servers/</link>
      <description>More context can mean more attack surfaces for your projects. Be prepared for what lies ahead with this guide. The post How to build secure and scalable remote MCP servers appeared first on The GitHub Blog.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 17:12:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://github.blog/ai-and-ml/generative-ai/how-to-build-secure-and-scalable-remote-mcp-servers/</guid>
      <source url="https://github.blog/feed/">GitHub Blog</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building competency is better than therapy</title>
      <link>https://world.hey.com/dhh/building-competency-is-better-than-therapy-4622c6b7</link>
      <description>The world is waking to the fact that talk therapy is neither the only nor the best way to cure a garden-variety petite depression. Something many people will encounter at some point in their lives. Studies have shown that exercise, for example, is a more effective treatment than talk therapy (and pharmaceuticals!) when dealing with such episodes. But I'm just as interested in the role building competence can have in warding off the demons.And partly because of this meme: I've talked about it before, but I keep coming back to the fact that it's exactly backwards. That signing up for an educational quest into Linux, history, or motorcycle repair actually is an incredibly effective alternative to therapy! At least for men who'd prefer to feel useful over being listened to, which, in my experience, is most of them.This is why I find it so misguided when people who undertake those quests sell their journey short with self-effacing jibes about how much an unattractive nerd it makes them to care about their hobby. Mihaly Csikszentmihalyi detailed back in 1990 how peak human happiness arrives exactly in these moments of flow when your competence is stretched by a difficult-but-doable challenge. Don't tell me those endorphins don't also help counter the darkness.But it's just as much about the fact that these pursuits of competence usually offer a great opportunity for community as well that seals the deal. I've found time and again that people are starved for the kind of topic-based connections that, say, learning about Linux offers in spades. You're not just learning, you're learning with others.That is a time-tested antidote to depression: Forming and cultivating meaningful human connections. Yes, doing so over the internet isn't as powerful as doing it in person, but it's still powerful. It still offers community, involvement, and plenty of invitation to carry a meaningful burden.Open source nails this trifecta of motivations to a T. There are endless paths of discovery and mastery available. There are tons of fellow travelers with whom to connect and collaborate. And you'll find an unlimited number of meaningful burdens in maintainerships open for the taking.So next time you see that meme, you should cheer that the talk therapy table is empty. Leave it available for the severe, pathological cases that exercise and the pursuit of competence can't cure. Most people just don't need therapy, they need purpose, they need competence, they need exercise, and they need community.</description>
      <pubDate>2025-07-25T15:16:53Z</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://world.hey.com/dhh/building-competency-is-better-than-therapy-4622c6b7</guid>
      <source url="https://world.hey.com/dhh/feed.atom">David Heinemeier Hansson</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What 85 years of research says is the real key to happiness | Robert Waldinger: Full Interview</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_CxmzkYPvsg</link>
      <description>“We can make ourselves more likely to be happy by building a life that includes the conditions that make for happiness.” Subscribe to Big Think on YouTube ► https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCvQECJukTDE2i6aCoMnS-Vg?sub_confirmation=1 Up next, Harvard professor’s 6-step guide to Zen Buddhism ► https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zBN5aa3jAHw What if the secret to lasting happiness has been hiding in plain sight? Harvard psychiatrist Robert Waldinger reveals insights from the world’s longest study on adult life, 85 years of data that challenge our assumptions about success, health, and fulfillment. Waldinger shares how our relationships and connections – not our wealth, fame, or success, directly boosts our minds, bodies, and longevity. 00:00:00 Part 1: Happiness. How did you get into psychiatry? 00:01:05 What is your research about? 00:05:35 How much control do we have over our happiness? 00:06:34 How do relationships affect happiness? 00:08:43 How do childhood experiences impact happiness? 00:11:44 How does evolutionary biology influence our happiness? 00:12:29 How do relationships impact physical health? 00:17:18 What is social fitness? 00:17:55 How do I maintain healthy relationships? 00:18:49 How can I evaluate my social fitness? 00:20:16 How does mapping my social universe contribute to my wellbeing? 00:22:11 If a relationship is depleting, what should I do? 00:23:42 How many close friends do I need? 00:24:43 What is your study's primary discovery? 00:29:16 What is your background with Zen? 00:29:52 How does Zen shape relationships? 00:31:30 What is the goal of Zen? 00:32:37 Why is impermanence helpful to consider? 00:34:53 How might the Four Noble Truths improve relationships? 00:37:51 How does understanding attachment help guide my relationships? 00:38:17 How does a "beginner's mind" benefit my relationships? 00:39:55 What is mindfulness and how do I cultivate it? 00:42:19 How does recognizing suffering improve relationships? 00:43:00 How does "metta" aid relationships? 00:44:31 What is enlightenment? 00:50:31 Do we have a loneliness epidemic? 00:53:26 What’s the difference between loneliness and isolation? 00:54:27 How does loneliness harm us physically? 00:56:12 What fundamental need do relationships satisfy? 00:58:27 Is our happiness only dictated by our close connections? 01:01:07 What can I do to lessen loneliness? Read the video transcript ► https://bigthink.com/series/full-interview/robert-waldinger-happiness/?utm_source=youtube&amp;utm_medium=video&amp;utm_campaign=youtube_description ---------------------------------------------------------------------------------- Go Deeper with Big Think: ►Become a Big Think Member Get exclusive content, early, ad-free access to new releases, and more. https://www.youtube.com/@bigthink/membership/ ►Get Big Think+ for Business Engage learners like never before with high-impact video microlearning from the biggest thinkers in the world. https://bigthink.com/plus/?utm_source=youtube&amp;utm_medium=video&amp;utm_campaign=youtube_description ---------------------------------------------------------------------------------- About Robert Waldinger: Robert Waldinger, MD is a Clinical Professor of Psychiatry at Harvard Medical School, a practicing psychiatrist, psychoanalyst, and a Zen teacher and practitioner. For the last two decades, Waldinger has been the director of the Harvard Study of Adult Development. This study, conducted over more than 85 years, has analyzed the entire lives of 724 families to determine the activities, behaviors, and dynamics that enhance a person’s life-long well-being. Waldinger has dedicated his career to examining these elements and discovering what brings true fulfillment to human existence. He is the author of several books, including his most recent, The Good Life: Lessons from the World’s Longest Scientific Study of Happiness.</description>
      <pubDate>2025-07-25T13:01:17+00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_CxmzkYPvsg</guid>
      <source url="https://www.youtube.com/feeds/videos.xml?channel_id=UCvQECJukTDE2i6aCoMnS-Vg">Big Think</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Around 6,000 porn sites start checking ages in UK</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/c24v4dl5r16o?at_medium=RSS&amp;at_campaign=rss</link>
      <description>Despite the law some remain sceptical about the effectiveness of porn age checks.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 11:30:21 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/c24v4dl5r16o?at_medium=RSS&amp;at_campaign=rss</guid>
      <source url="http://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/technology/rss.xml">BBC Technology</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saving the world with speed and at scale</title>
      <link>https://stackoverflow.blog/2025/07/25/saving-the-world-with-speed-and-at-scale/</link>
      <description>Ryan Panchadsaram, co-author of Speed and Scale, sits down on the podcast to explore the role of developers in combating climate change, how efficient coding practices help lower emissions, and how developers can contribute to open-source projects through GitHub’s Climate Action Plan that help drive forward sustainable technologies.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 07:40:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://stackoverflow.blog/2025/07/25/saving-the-world-with-speed-and-at-scale/</guid>
      <source url="https://stackoverflow.blog/feed/">Stack Overflow Blog</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Artificial food colours are out, so what's next?</title>
      <link>https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/c4g83dpeendo?at_medium=RSS&amp;at_campaign=rss</link>
      <description>Big food firms are phasing out artificial colours, so tech firms are rushing to fill the gap.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 23:01:09 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/c4g83dpeendo?at_medium=RSS&amp;at_campaign=rss</guid>
      <source url="http://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/technology/rss.xml">BBC Technology</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You expect principles but should wish for none</title>
      <link>https://world.hey.com/dhh/you-expect-principles-but-should-wish-for-none-531988ec</link>
      <description>People seem to be continuously disappointed by the fact that public companies are run by professional managers who don't operate from deep principles. But they shouldn't be. It's in everyone's interest that corporations set their sails to the wind and whims of the prevailing culture. It's the essence of capitalism: Give people what they want (especially when they change their minds)! Now, as an owner-operator, I can afford to have unpopular principles from time to time. I can afford to earn less than the theoretical maximum from the market as a consequence of these principles. That's because I'm playing with my own money. That's the privilege of being privately held.But even the most powerful professional CEO is on a short leash from the company's real owners, the shareholders. This is often maligned as the root of all evil in modern capitalism. That we've divorced the owner and the operator. And I think there's a worthy critique of that arrangement to be had, like Burnham in The Managerial Society. But I also think not enough appreciation is afforded this arrangement.Shareholders, in their Platonic ideal, only care about maximizing profits. That can occasionally be an incentive for amoral behavior, but more often, it's simply a driver towards making stuff that people want. Not what they say they want, but what they actually buy. That's why libertarians love to talk about the free-market economy as an information system. Supply-side economics notwithstanding, demand directs production and judges the contestants. If you don't make something people want, they won't buy it, and you'll soon be out of business.I thought about this today because of two popular marketing campaigns currently running in America. The one by Nike celebrating family, the other by American Eagle celebrating "good jeans". Here's a comparison someone made online using these companies' campaigns from the early 2020s and now: Quite the contrast! Almost looks like hypocrisy, doesn't it? How can you celebrate obesity one moment, then hour-glass ideals the next? How can you embrace undirected individualism before, then exalt family values at the height of excellence now?Easy: The vibe changed. Demand changed. Selling 2020 woke platitudes into a 2025 market is a clear way to lose your job as a professional manager. Because it's no longer what people want.Hell, it's most likely not even the same managers making these diametrically-opposed value judgments. Perhaps not even managers at all, but marketing agencies in tune with said prevailing culture. The big information system of commerce is sending a billion packets of intent all day long and the current message is now crystal clear: Blond babies and boobs are back in business!This was the original killer insight by the architects of the short-lived woke theocracy: If you can capture culture, you can capture capitalism. But it's one thing to capture culture, it's quite another to hold it.So now much of mainstream American culture has simply reverted to the roots of capitalism: Making things that most people want. By course-correcting the culture, we've course-corrected commerce. No corporate principles required.</description>
      <pubDate>2025-07-24T19:28:08Z</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://world.hey.com/dhh/you-expect-principles-but-should-wish-for-none-531988ec</guid>
      <source url="https://world.hey.com/dhh/feed.atom">David Heinemeier Hansson</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to streamline GitHub API calls in Azure Pipelines</title>
      <link>https://github.blog/enterprise-software/ci-cd/how-to-streamline-github-api-calls-in-azure-pipelines/</link>
      <description>Build a custom Azure DevOps extension that eliminates the complexity of JWT generation and token management, enabling powerful automation and enhanced security controls. The post How to streamline GitHub API calls in Azure Pipelines appeared first on The GitHub Blog.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://github.blog/enterprise-software/ci-cd/how-to-streamline-github-api-calls-in-azure-pipelines/</guid>
      <source url="https://github.blog/feed/">GitHub Blog</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 5 Times Life on Earth Almost Ended</title>
      <link>https://www.youtube.com/shorts/IZ55YvFE960</link>
      <description>Life on Earth has nearly ended five times, and it may be happening again right now. From massive volcanic eruptions to deadly asteroids and algae gone wild, mass extinction events have wiped out over 99% of all species that ever lived. #kurzgesagt #inanutshell #kurzgesagt_inanutshell #learnwithshorts #science Sources &amp; further reading: https://sites.google.com/view/kgs-tiktok-sources Follow us for more sciencey content! 🦆 OUR CHANNELS ▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀ German: https://kgs.link/youtubeDE Spanish: https://kgs.link/youtubeES French: https://kgs.link/youtubeFR Portuguese: https://kgs.link/youtubePT Arabic: https://kgs.link/youtubeAR Hindi: https://kgs.link/youtubeHI Japanese: https://kgs.link/youtubeJA Korean: https://kgs.link/youtubeKO HOW CAN YOU SUPPORT US? ▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀ This is how we make our living and it would be a pleasure if you support us! Get Products designed with ❤ https://shop.kgs.link/shorts Become a Part of kurzgesagt by joining the Patreon Bird Army 🐧 https://kgs.link/patreon DISCUSSIONS &amp; SOCIAL MEDIA ▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀ Instagram: https://kgs.link/instagram TikTok: https://kgs.link/tiktok Reddit: https://kgs.link/reddit Discord: https://kgs.link/discord Twitter: https://kgs.link/twitter Bluesky: https://kgs.link/bluesky Facebook: https://kgs.link/facebook Newsletter: https://kgs.link/newsletter OUR VOICE ▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀ The Kurzgesagt voice is from Steve Taylor: https://kgs.link/youtube-voice OUR MUSIC ♬♪ ▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀▀ 700+ minutes of Kurzgesagt Soundtracks by Epic Mountain: Spotify: https://kgs.link/music-spotify Soundcloud: https://kgs.link/music-soundcloud Bandcamp: https://kgs.link/music-bandcamp Youtube: https://kgs.link/music-youtube Facebook: https://kgs.link/music-facebook</description>
      <pubDate>2025-07-24T14:00:34+00:00</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.youtube.com/shorts/IZ55YvFE960</guid>
      <source url="https://www.youtube.com/feeds/videos.xml?channel_id=UCsXVk37bltHxD1rDPwtNM8Q">Kurzgesagt – In a Nutshell</source>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>